Teen Kar Seng

Email: teenkar@gmail.com Based in: Singapore

Phone: (+65) 9722 7928

Professional Summary

I am a Senior year student at Berklee College of Music (Berklee Online) pursuing a Bachelor of Arts in Songwriting and Producing Music.

I am able to compose, notate, arrange, orchestrate and produce music for a variety of genres and use cases. I am also highly proficient with Pro Tools and experienced in audio editing, mixing and sound design. I have worked on several student projects throughout my coursework.

My other competencies include video editing, graphic design and photography, having graduated with a diploma in Communications & Media Management from Temasek Polytechnic.

Education

Bachelor of Arts, Songwriting and Producing Music, Berklee College of Music (Berklee Online), Boston, Massachusetts.

April 2020 - Present

Current CGPA: 3.99

Diploma, Communications and Media Management, Temasek Polytechnic, Singapore.

April 2016 - May 2019

• Graduated CGPA: 3.48

Skills

Avid ProTools
Audiokinetic Wwise
FMOD Studios
Unity Engine (Basic)
Adobe Premiere Pro
Adobe Photoshop
Adobe After Effects

Sound Design
Music Production
Music Writing
HTML/CSS & JavaScript
Video Production
Photography
Microsoft Office

Experience

Freelance Audio Editor

May 2021

• Performed recording, editing and mixing of voice-overs for a college level prototype product design video.

Marketing Intern MediaCorp Pte Ltd, Singapore

April 2018 - September 2018

- Filmed and edited videos for social media marketing.
- Graphic Design to create posters and banners for use on digital website and printed for physical use.
- Collaborated with team members to help expand marketing channels.
- Monitored and analyzed impressions, reach and engagements on social media marketing campaigns.
- Handled social media accounts for company.

Military

National Service, Republic of Singapore Air Force (RSAF)

May 2019 - May 2021

• 2-year mandatory enlistment to the Singapore National Service with the RSAF.

Language

- English (Spoken, Written) First Language
- Mandarin Chinese (Spoken, Written) Proficient

Achievements

- MediaCorp Major Project Prize for Best Major Project Group, 2019
- 3rd Place at POL-ITE Water Polo competition, 2017 & 2018
- The Dream Composition Songwriting Competition Finalist, 2018
- 4th Place at National B Division Floorball competition, 2015
- ABRSM Grade 8 Practical (Piano)
- ABRSM Grade 5 Theory